

KAMIL MAZELANIK

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

City: Rybnik

Phone: 500 036 580

Mail: kamilmaz9206@gmail.com

Linkedin:

http://www.linkedin.com/in/kamil-

mazelanik

GitHub: https://github.com/Kaweight

TECHNICAL SKILLS

TypeScript

JavaScript ES5, ES6+

React.is

 React libraries (Redux, Router etc.)

Webpack

CSS

SCSS, Sass

HTML

Bootstrap

Git

Jira

LANGUAGES

English: communicative (B2)

Polish: native

INTERESTS

Handmade projects

Drawing

Motorsport, CrossFit

I hereby give consent for my personal data to be processed for the purpose of conducting recruitment for the position for which I am applying.

ABOUT ME

I am an ambitious frontend developer who has been working professionally for 2 years. I am an engineer by education with a degree in management and production engineering, but 4 years ago I decided to change my career path. I have been developing my skills towards the frontend. In 2021, I started working with Ework where I work on developing applications in JavaScript + React, among other technologies. On a daily basis I use: version control system - GIT and Jira software. I find myself well in a team. My goal, both professional and private, is to constantly improve and become a better frontend developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Ework Group

August 2021 – present Warsaw, Poland

My responsibilities:

- Developing and expanding application features.
- Creating reusable components according to design system.
- Working in a scrum team.
- Contacting and collaborating with project managers, backend/frontend developers and designers.
- Providing responsive views.
- Working with the GitLab platform code review, application deployment.
- Estimating tasks.
- Bug fixing.

Non - IT related works

2013 - 2021

Constructor/ Designer working in CAD programs.

COURSES

Bootcamp Front-end: React

Kodilla Programming school 07.2020 - 11.2020

Scope of training: HTML, CSS, RWD, Sass, Bootstrap, Git, JavaScript ES6, AJAX React, Redux, React Router.

Other online courses

Web development courses on platforms such as Udemy (e.g. TypeScript, JavaScript, React.js, Git)

EDUCATION

Silesian University of Technology in Gliwice

Management and Production Engineering, Engineering degree – 09.2014 - 03.2018 Specialty - Production Systems Management